Finding aid to the Athletics Subject Files CA.MS.00167
Smith College Archives
Athletics Subject Files
1800-2016
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Department of Athletics
CA.MS.00167
17.625 linear feet (43 containers)
8.66 Megabytes (8 .jpg and .png files)
The Athletics Subject Files contain a wide range of information about the history of sport at Smith College.
Conditions Governing Access
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Athletics Subject Files were donated to the Smith College Archives over a period of time from a variety of sources, including the Department of Athletics.
Biographical / Historical
Athletics have been an important part of Smith College life since Senda Berenson started the program in the late 1800's. The first women's collegiate basketball game was held at Smith in 1893 after Berenson adapted the game for women. For many years, all freshmen and sophomores were required to take a sport as part of their regular studies. The Smith College Athletic Association prevented intercollegiate competition, maintaining that it would hurt the spirit of friendly intramural competition at the college, but the intramural programs drew much interest, and spots on class teams were highly coveted. The first intercollegiate games were allowed in 1971, and Smith College joined the Northeast Intercollegiate Athletic Conference. In 1981, Smith became the first women's college to join the NCAA, in which it remains a division III member today.
Related Materials
42. Dorothy Ainsworth Papers
42. Senda Berenson Papers
52. Physical Education Department Records
80. Athletic Association Records
Scope and Contents
The Athletics Subject files contain materials describing the various sports and sports-related activities at Smith College. The files include sports played both officially and unofficially, on an intramural or intercollegiate basis. They also include records of outdoors activities and clubs, and events involving athletics demonstrations, such as Field Day and Float Night. The basketball files within the collection also include general basketball history. Types of materials include photographs, news clippings, game scores, team lists, pamphlets, programs, ticket stubs, rules, and newsletters.
Please note that early athletics games were held between class years. Therefore, any information from a particular year or game might be found either in the year of the event or in the class years of the participants.
Smith College. Department of Athletics
- Archery
  - Archery, 1916-1923 (Box 1343, Folder 1)
  - Archery, 1927-28 (Box 1343, Folder 2)
  - Archery, 1931 (Box 1343, Folder 3)
  - Archery, 1932 (Box 1343, Folder 4)
  - Archery, 1934-1935 (Box 1343, Folder 5)
  - Archery, 1936 (Box 1343, Folder 6)
  - Archery, 1937-1939 (Box 1343, Folder 7)
  - Archery, 1940s (Box 1343, Folder 8)
  - Archery, 1950 (Box 1343, Folder 9)
  - Archery, 1950s (Box 1343, Folder 10)
  - Archery, 1960-ongoing (Box 1343, Folder 11)
  - Archery, undated (Box 1343, Folder 12)
  - Record Book, 1912-1932 (Box 1343, Folder 13)
  - Record Book (papers from), 1912-1932 (Box 1343, Folder 14)
  - Record Book, 1932-1957 (Box 1343, Folder 15)
  - Record Book (papers from), 1932-1957 (Box 1343, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Teams (unlabled photographs), 2004-2005; undated (Box 1343, Folder 17)
- Badminton
  - Badminton: Record Book, 1931-1967 (Box 1344, Folder 1)
  - Badminton: Record Book, Loose Contents, 1931-1967 (Box 1344, Folder 2)
  - Badminton, 1930s (Box 1344, Folder 3)
  - Badminton, 1940s (Box 1344, Folder 4)
  - Badminton, 1950s (Box 1344, Folder 5)
  - Badminton, 1960-ongoing (Box 1344, Folder 6)
- Baseball
  - Baseball: General, 1916-1947 (Box 1344, Folder 7)
  - Baseball, 1890-1915 (Box 1344, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 1916-1947 (Box 1344, Folder 9)
  - Baseball: Photos, 1920s-1930s (Box 1344, Folder 10)
  - Baseball: Photos, 1949-1950s (Box 1344, Folder 11)
  - Baseball: Photos, 1970s (Box 1344, Folder 12)
  - Baseball, 1980-1981 (Box 1344, Folder 13)
  - Baseball, 1981-1982 (Box 1344, Folder 14)
  - Baseball, 1983-1984 (Box 1344, Folder 15)
  - Baseball, 1984-1985 (Box 1344, Folder 16)
  - Baseball, 1985-1986 (Box 1344, Folder 17)
  - Baseball, 1986-1987 (Box 1344, Folder 18)
  - Baseball, 1987-1988 (Box 1344, Folder 19)
  - Baseball, 1988-1989 (Box 1344, Folder 20)
  - Baseball, 1989-1990 (Box 1344, Folder 21)
  - Baseball, 1990-1991 (Box 1344, Folder 22)
  - Baseball, 1991-1992 (Box 1344, Folder 23)
- Basketball
  - General: Scrapbook pages, badges, songs, tickets, 1897-1913 (Box 1345, Folder 1)
  - History: General (Box 1345, Folder 2)
  - History: 90th Anniversary, 1983 (Box 1345, Folder 3)
  - History: Basketball Hall of Fame and Women-Debate and Dedication, 1983-1989 (Box 1345, Folder 4)
  - History: Centennial, 1991-1993 (Box 1345, Folder 5)
  - Photos for book: Basketball for Women, 1903 (Box 1345, Folder 6)
  - Basketball, 1893-1894 (Box 1345, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1895; 1931 (Box 1345, Folder 8)
  - Basketball 1895: Photographs- backed, 1892-1895 (Box 1345, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1895: Photos- unbacked, 1892-1895 (Box 1345, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1896: Clippings, 1893-1896 (Box 1345, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1896: Photographs- backed, 1893-1896 (Box 1345, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1896: Photographs- unbacked, 1893-1896 (Box 1345, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1897: Clippings and Songs, 1894-1897 (Box 1345, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1897: Photographs- backed, 1894-1897 (Box 1345, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1897: Photographs- backed, 1894-1897 (Box 1345, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1897: Photographs- unbacked, 1894-1897 (Box 1345, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1898: Clippings, 1895-1898 (Box 1345, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1898: Photographs- backed, 1895-1898 (Box 1345, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1898: Photographs- unbacked, 1895-1898 (Box 1345, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1899: Clippings, Songs, Ticket, 1896-1899 (Box 1345, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1899: Photographs- backed, 1896-1899 (Box 1345, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1899: Photographs- unbacked, 1896-1899 (Box 1345, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1900: Clippings, Sign, 1897-1900 (Box 1345, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1900: Photographs- backed, 1897-1900 (Box 1345, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1900: Photographs- unbacked, 1897-1900 (Box 1345, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1901: Clippings and Letter, 1898-1901 (Box 1346, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1901: Photographs- backed, 1898-1901 (Box 1346, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1901: Photographs- unbacked, 1898-1901 (Box 1346, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1902: Photographs- backed, 1899-1902 (Box 1346, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1902: Songs, 1899-1902 (Box 1346, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1902: Photographs- unbacked, 1899-1902 (Box 1346, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1903: Clippings, Scrapbook page, 1900-1903 (Box 1346, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1903: Photographs- unbacked, 1900-1903 (Box 1346, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1904: Photographs- backed, 1901-1904 (Box 1346, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1904: Photographs- unbacked, 1901-1904 (Box 1346, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1905: Photographs- backed, 1902-1905 (Box 1346, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1905: Photographs- not backed, 1902-1905 (Box 1346, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1906: Clippings, 1903-1906 (Box 1346, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1906: Photographs- backed, 1903-1906 (Box 1346, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1906: Photographs- unbacked, 1903-1906 (Box 1346, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1907: Clippings, 1904-1907 (Box 1346, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1907: Photographs- unbacked, 1904-1907 (Box 1346, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1908: Photographs- backed, 1905-1908 (Box 1346, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1908: Photographs- unbacked, 1905-1908 (Box 1346, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1909 Clippings, 1906-1909 (Box 1346, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1909 Photographs- backed, 1906-1909 (Box 1346, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1909 Photographs- unbacked, 1906-1909 (Box 1346, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1910: Ticket, Clippings (Box 1346.1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1910: Photographs, backed, 1907-1910 (Box 1346.1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1910: Photographs, unbacked, 1907-1910 (Box 1346.1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1911, 1908-1911 (Box 1346.1, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1912, 1909-1912 (Box 1346.1, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1913, 1910-1913 (Box 1346.1, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1914, 1911-1914 (Box 1346.1, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1915, 1912-1915 (Box 1346.1, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1916 (Box 1346.1, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1917, 1914-1917 (Box 1346.1, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1918, 1915-1918 (Box 1346.1, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1919 and 1920, 1914-1920 (Box 1346.1, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1921-22 Clippings, 1921-1922 (Box 1346.1, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1922 and Photos taken 1921-22, 1921-1922 (Box 1346.1, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1923, 1920-1923 (Box 1346.1, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1924, 1921-1924 (Box 1346.1, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1925-1926, 1922-1926 (Box 1346.1, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1927-1928, 1924-1928 (Box 1346.1, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1929, 1926-1929 (Box 1346.1, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1929-1930 (Box 1346.1, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1930-31 Press Releases, 1930-1931 (Box 1346.1, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1931-32 Photographs, 1928-1932 (Box 1346.1, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1932-33, 1932-1933 (Box 1346.1, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1933-34, 1933-1934 (Box 1346.1, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1934-35, 1934-1935 (Box 1346.1, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1935-36, 1935-1936 (Box 1346.1, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1936-37, 1936-1937 (Box 1346.1, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1937-38, 1937-1938 (Box 1346.1, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1939-40, 1939-1940 (Box 1346.1, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1940-41, 1937-1941 (Box 1346.1, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1940-c.1950, Photos only, 1940-1950 (Box 1346.1, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1944-49, Photos only, 1944-1949 (Box 1346.1, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1950-52, 1950-1952 (Box 1346.1, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1953-59, 1953-1959 (Box 1346.1, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1950-1970 Photographs (Box 1346.1, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1970s (Box 1346.1, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1978-79, 1978-1979 (Box 1346.1, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1979-80, 1979-1980 (Box 1346.1, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 1346.1, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 1346.1, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1982-83, 1982-1983 (Box 1346.1, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1983-84, 1983-1984 (Box 1346.1, Folder 42)
  - Basketball, 1984-1985 (Box 1347, Folder 1)
  - Basketball, 1985-1986 (Box 1347, Folder 2)
  - Basketball, 1986-1987 (Box 1347, Folder 3)
  - Basketball, 1987-1988 (Box 1347, Folder 4)
  - Basketball, 1988-1989 (Box 1347, Folder 5)
  - Basketball, 1989-1990 (Box 1347, Folder 6)
  - Basketball, 1990-1992 (Box 1347, Folder 7)
  - Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 1347, Folder 8)
  - Basketball: Centennial, 1992-1993 (Box 1347, Folder 9)
  - Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 1347, Folder 10)
  - Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 1347, Folder 11)
  - Basketball, 1995-1996 (Box 1347, Folder 12)
  - Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 1347, Folder 13)
  - Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 1347, Folder 14)
  - Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 1347, Folder 15)
  - Basketball, 1999-ongoing (Box 1347, Folder 16)
  - Photos, dates unknown, undated (Box 1347, Folder 17)
  - Record Book (bound), 1931-1954 (Box 1347, Folder 18)
  - Record Book (bound), 1954-1981 (Box 1347, Folder 19)
  - Record Book, 1913-1931 (Box 1347.1, Folder 1)
  - Record Book, loose papers, 1931-1954 (Box 1347.1, Folder 2)
  - Record Book, 1937-1940 (Box 1347.1, Folder 3)
  - Record Book, 1940-1943 (Box 1347.1, Folder 4)
  - Record Book, 1943-1946 (Box 1347.1, Folder 5)
  - Record Book, 1946-1949 (Box 1347.1, Folder 6)
  - Record Book, 1949-1951 (Box 1347.1, Folder 7)
  - Record Book, 1951-1953 (Box 1347.1, Folder 8)
  - Record Book, 1953-1955 (Box 1347.1, Folder 9)
- Bicyles
  - Bicycles: General, 1897; 1926; undated (Box 1348, Folder 1)
  - Bicycles, early 1900s (Box 1348, Folder 2)
  - Bicycles, 1920s (Box 1348, Folder 3)
  - Bicycles, 1930s (Box 1348, Folder 4)
  - Bicycles, 1940s (Box 1348, Folder 5)
  - Bicycles, 1949-1950 (Box 1348, Folder 6)
  - Bicycles, 1950s (Box 1348, Folder 7)
  - Bicycles, 1960s (Box 1348, Folder 8)
  - Bicycles, 1970s (Box 1348, Folder 9)
  - Bicycles, 1980s (Box 1348, Folder 10)
  - Bicycles, undated (Box 1348, Folder 11)
  - Bicycles - Cycling Club, 1992-1993 (Box 1348, Folder 12)
  - Bicycles - Cycling Club, 1993-1994 (Box 1348, Folder 13)
- Blazers: All-Smith Blazers, Clippings, 1921-1965 (Box 1349, Folder 1)
- Blazers: All-Smith Blazers, Photographs, 1936-1948 (Box 1349, Folder 2)
- Bowling, 1936-1964 (Box 1349, Folder 3)
- Bowling, Table Tennis: Record Book, 1932-1978 (Box 1349, Folder 4)
- Canoe and Row
  - Canoe and Row, 1900-1950 (Box 1349, Folder 5)
  - Canoe and Row, 1950-ongoing (Box 1349, Folder 6)
  - Canoeing: Record Book, 1944-1979 (Box 1349, Folder 7)
- Club Sports, 2002-03 (Box 1349, Folder 8)
- Crew
  - Clippings, 1900-1950s (Box 1350, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1933-1934 (Box 1350, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1934-1935 (Box 1350, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1935-1936 (Box 1350, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1970s (Box 1350, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 1350, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 1350, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 1350, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 1350, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 1350, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 1350, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 1350, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 1350, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 1350, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 1350, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 1350, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 1350, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 1350, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1994-ongoing (Box 1350, Folder 19)
  - Inter-house Competition, 1944-1951 (Box 1350, Folder 20)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1936-1939 (Box 1350, Folder 21)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1939-1945 (Box 1350, Folder 22)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1944-1948 (Box 1350, Folder 23)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1948-1952 (Box 1350, Folder 24)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1952-1955 (Box 1350, Folder 25)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1955-1958 (Box 1350, Folder 26)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1958-1961 (Box 1350, Folder 27)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1961-1966 (Box 1350, Folder 28)
  - Manager's Notebook, 1966-1973 (Box 1350, Folder 29)
  - Manager's Notebook, undated (Box 1350, Folder 30)
  - Notes By Prudence Wallis, 1936 (Box 1350, Folder 31)
  - Notes By Prudence Wallis, 1936 (Box 1350, Folder 32)
  - Photographs, 1917 (Box 1350, Folder 33)
  - Photographs, 1918 (Box 1350, Folder 34)
  - Photographs, 1922 (Box 1350, Folder 35)
  - Photographs, 1923 (Box 1350, Folder 36)
  - Photographs, 1924 (Box 1350, Folder 37)
  - Photographs, 1925-1927 (Box 1350, Folder 38)
  - Photographs, 1928 (Box 1350, Folder 39)
  - Photographs, 1929 (Box 1350, Folder 40)
  - Photographs, 1931 (Box 1350, Folder 41)
  - Photographs, 1932 (Box 1350, Folder 42)
  - Photographs, 1933-1934 (Box 1350, Folder 43)
  - Photographs, 1937 (Box 1350, Folder 44)
  - Photographs, 1938 (Box 1350, Folder 45)
  - Photographs, 1939 (Box 1350, Folder 46)
  - Photographs, 1940-1944 (Box 1350, Folder 47)
  - Photographs, 1945-1946 (Box 1350, Folder 48)
  - Photographs, 1947-1948 (Box 1350, Folder 49)
  - Photographs, 1949 (Box 1350, Folder 50)
  - Photographs, 1951 (Box 1351, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1952-1953 (Box 1351, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1954 (Box 1351, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1956-1960 (Box 1351, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1961-1962 (Box 1351, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1963-1965 (Box 1351, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1965-1966 (Box 1351, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, 1966-1968 (Box 1351, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, 1974-1978 (Box 1351, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1979-1980 (Box 1351, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 1981-1982 (Box 1351, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 1982-1983 (Box 1351, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 1983-1984 (Box 1351, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 1984-1985 (Box 1351, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1985-1986 (Box 1351, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, 1986-1987 (Box 1351, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, 1987-1988 (Box 1351, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, 1988-1989 (Box 1351, Folder 18)
  - Photographs, 1989-1990 (Box 1351, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, 1990-1991 (Box 1351, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 1991-1992 (Box 1351, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 1351, Folder 22)
  - Photographs, 1993-1994 (Box 1351, Folder 23)
  - Photographs, 1994-ongoing (Box 1351, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1351, Folder 25)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1351, Folder 26)
  - Record Book, 1916-1935 (Box 1352, Folder 1)
  - Record Book, 1935-1939 (Box 1352, Folder 2)
  - Record Book, 1938-1982 (Box 1352, Folder 3)
  - Record Book, 1973-1984 (Box 1352, Folder 4)
- Cricket, 1914-21; 1974 (Box 1353, Folder 1)
- Cricket Record Book, 1912-26 (Box 1353, Folder 2)
- Croquet, 1907-10; 1990-95 (Box 1353, Folder 3)
- Cross-Country
  - Cross-Country, 1981-1984 (Box 1353, Folder 4)
  - Cross-Country, 1984-1985 (Box 1353, Folder 5)
  - Cross-Country, 1985-1986 (Box 1353, Folder 6)
  - Cross-Country, 1986-1987 (Box 1353, Folder 7)
  - Cross-Country, 1987-1988 (Box 1353, Folder 8)
  - Cross-Country, 1988-1989 (Box 1353, Folder 9)
  - Cross-Country, 1989-1990 (Box 1353, Folder 10)
  - Cross-Country, 1990-1991 (Box 1353, Folder 11)
  - Cross-Country, 1991-1993 (Box 1353, Folder 12)
  - Cross-Country, 1994-1995 (Box 1353, Folder 13)
  - Cross-Country, 1995-1997 (Box 1353, Folder 14)
  - Cross-Country, 1999-ongoing (Box 1353, Folder 15)
  - Cross-Country, undated (Box 1353, Folder 16)
- Dance, 1941; 1978 (Box 1354, Folder 1)
- Discus Throwing, 1929 (Box 1354, Folder 2)
- Fencing
  - Fencing: Clippings, 1929-1953 (Box 1354, Folder 3)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1904 (Box 1354, Folder 4)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1920s (Box 1354, Folder 5)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1930s (Box 1354, Folder 6)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1934 (Box 1354, Folder 7)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1937 (Box 1354, Folder 8)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1939-1940 (Box 1354, Folder 9)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1946 (Box 1354, Folder 10)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1950s (Box 1354, Folder 11)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1960-1979 (Box 1354, Folder 12)
  - Fencing: Photos, 1980-ongoing (Box 1354, Folder 13)
  - Fencing: Record Book, 1928-1973 (Box 1354, Folder 14)
- Field Day and Float Night
  - Field Day and Float Night, General, 1916-1922; undated (Box 1354, Folder 15)
  - Field Day, 1910 (Box 1354, Folder 16)
  - Field Day, 1911 (Box 1354, Folder 17)
  - Field Day, 1912 (Box 1354, Folder 18)
  - Field Day, 1913 (Box 1354, Folder 19)
  - Field Day, 1914 (Box 1354, Folder 20)
  - Field Day, 1915 (Box 1354, Folder 21)
  - Field Day, 1916 (Box 1354, Folder 22)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1917 (Box 1354, Folder 23)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1918 (Box 1354, Folder 24)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1919 (Box 1354, Folder 25)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1920 (Box 1354, Folder 26)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1921 (Box 1354, Folder 27)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1922 (Box 1354, Folder 28)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1923 (Box 1354, Folder 29)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1924 (Box 1354, Folder 30)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1925 (Box 1355, Folder 1)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1926 (Box 1355, Folder 2)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1927 (Box 1355, Folder 3)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1928 (Box 1355, Folder 4)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1929 (Box 1355, Folder 5)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1930 (Box 1355, Folder 6)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1931 (Box 1355, Folder 7)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1932 (Box 1355, Folder 8)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1933 (Box 1355, Folder 9)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1934 (Box 1355, Folder 10)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1935 (Box 1355, Folder 11)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1936 (Box 1355, Folder 12)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1937 (Box 1355, Folder 13)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1938 (Box 1355, Folder 14)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1939 (Box 1355, Folder 15)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1940 (Box 1355, Folder 16)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1941 (Box 1355, Folder 17)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1942 (Box 1355, Folder 18)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1943 (Box 1355, Folder 19)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1944 (Box 1355, Folder 20)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1946 (Box 1355, Folder 21)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1947 (Box 1355, Folder 22)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1948 (Box 1355, Folder 23)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1949 (Box 1355, Folder 24)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1950 (Box 1355, Folder 25)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1951 (Box 1356, Folder 1)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1952 (Box 1356, Folder 2)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1953 (Box 1356, Folder 3)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1954 (Box 1356, Folder 4)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1955 (Box 1356, Folder 5)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1956 (Box 1356, Folder 6)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1957 (Box 1356, Folder 7)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1958 (Box 1356, Folder 8)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1959 (Box 1356, Folder 9)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1960 (Box 1356, Folder 10)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1961 (Box 1356, Folder 11)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1962-1963 (Box 1356, Folder 12)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1964 (Box 1356, Folder 13)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1965 (Box 1356, Folder 14)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1966-1967 (Box 1356, Folder 15)
  - Field Day and Float Night, 1968-1972 (Box 1356, Folder 16)
  - Field Day and Float Night, undated (Box 1356, Folder 17)
  - Field Day: Octoberfest, 1993 (Box 1356, Folder 18)
  - Field Day, 1996 (Box 1356, Folder 19)
  - Float Night: Instructions, undated (Box 1356, Folder 20)
  - Float Night Notebook, 1957-1969 (Box 1356, Folder 21)
- Folk Dancing Record Book, 1948-1976 (Box 1356, Folder 22)
- Football (Box 1357, Folder 1)
- Freshman Day
  - Freshman Day, 1930s (Box 1357, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Day, 1940s (Box 1357, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Day, 1950-1955 (Box 1357, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Day, 1956-1959 (Box 1357, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Day, 1960-1965 (Box 1357, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Day, 1966-1967 (Box 1357, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Day, 1968-1980 (Box 1357, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Day, undated (Box 1357, Folder 9)
- Golf
  - Golf, 1897 (Box 1358, Folder 1)
  - Golf, 1898-1900 (Box 1358, Folder 2)
  - Golf, 1901-1925 (Box 1358, Folder 3)
  - Golf, 1925-1931 (Box 1358, Folder 4)
  - Golf, 1932-1940 (Box 1358, Folder 5)
  - Golf, 1940s (Box 1358, Folder 6)
  - Golf, 1950s (Box 1358, Folder 7)
  - Golf, 1960-1979 (Box 1358, Folder 8)
  - Golf, 1980-ongoing (Box 1358, Folder 9)
  - Golf, undated (Box 1358, Folder 10)
  - Golf: Record Book, 1934-1982 (Box 1358, Folder 11)
- Gymnastics
  - Gymnastics, 1880s (Box 1358, Folder 12)
  - Gymnastics, 1923 (Box 1358, Folder 13)
  - Gymnastics, 1970s (Box 1358, Folder 14)
  - Gymnastics, 1979-1980 (Box 1358, Folder 15)
  - Gymnastics, 1981-1982 (Box 1358, Folder 16)
  - Gymnastics, 1982-1983 (Box 1358, Folder 17)
  - Gymnastics, 1983-1984 (Box 1358, Folder 18)
  - Gymnastics, 1984-1985 (Box 1358, Folder 19)
  - Gymnastics, 1985-1986 (Box 1358, Folder 20)
  - Gymnastics, 1986-1987 (Box 1358, Folder 21)
  - Gymnastics, 1987-1988 (Box 1358, Folder 22)
  - Gymnastics: Record Book, 1957-1979 (Box 1358, Folder 23)
- Hockey, Field
  - Hockey, Field, 1901-1904 (Box 1359, Folder 1)
  - Hockey, Field, 1905-1910 (Box 1359, Folder 2)
  - Hockey, Field, 1910-1911 (Box 1359, Folder 3)
  - Hockey, Field, 1912 (Box 1359, Folder 4)
  - Hockey, Field, 1914 (Box 1359, Folder 5)
  - Hockey, Field, 1915-1916 (Box 1359, Folder 6)
  - Hockey, Field, 1919-1926 (Box 1359, Folder 7)
  - Hockey, Field, 1928-1929 (Box 1359, Folder 8)
  - Hockey, Field, 1930 (Box 1359, Folder 9)
  - Hockey, Field, 1931 (Box 1359, Folder 10)
  - Hockey, Field, 1932 (Box 1359, Folder 11)
  - Hockey, Field, 1933-1934 (Box 1359, Folder 12)
  - Hockey, Field, 1935-1938 (Box 1359, Folder 13)